A Guide to the Atcheson L. Hench Autograph Collection
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Collection of Modern Autographs
  - 1873 December 23 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to [James R.] Osgood and Company, discusses his difficulties in getting the correct number of copies of his books, Cameos Selected from the Works of Walter Savage Landor by E.C. Stedman and T.B. Aldrich; with an introduction and The Poetical Works of Edmund Clarence Stedman, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:32)
  - 1879 April 13 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to Karl Knortz (1841-1918), writes "we really have a dearth of young poets - except such as you will find in the versed ed. Of Griswold's "Poets of America" & Female Poets of America" - brought down by Stoddard to a recent date - and such as you will learn of through their contributions to the leading magazines." Both sides of a note card (6435) (Box-folder 11:33)
  - 1894 January 18 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to Mrs. Putnam, declines her invitation, as he is avoiding going out due to his health, both sides of a note card (6435) (Box-folder 11:34)
  - 1888 December 5 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to [William Henry] Rideing (1853-1919), promises to send him an impression of the engraving Harpers published in Lathrop's article on New York literary life and "this one if far handsomer than any Stedman ever was - romantically flattering, & calculated to make Mrs. Rideing pronounce me a humbug if I ever have the luck to call upon you." Both sides of a note card (6435) (Box-folder 11:35)
  - 1895 October 20 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to [William Henry] Rideing (1853-1919), apologizes for his delay in responding to his card, having only last night completed his labors on two works over a period of two years., 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:35)
  - n.d. Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to [William Henry] Rideing (1853-1919), writes that the exhibition of Brown's paintings has officially closed but after telephoning the Century Club, the steward says he will let Rideing see the paintings if he arrives early on Monday morning, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:35)
  - 187[8] March 13 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to Charles Warren Stoddard (1843-1909), helps arrange a meeting between Stoddard and Messers. Smith and Holland for work on four or five South Sea sketches in his best manner as good as The Prodigal in Tahiti of not less than six pages each, and tells him to "please offer H. his choice of subjects, western or European, try to please him in your interview, 2 pages on a memorandum form. (6435) (Box-folder 11:36)
  - 1897 December 10 Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908) to Mr. Tapley, declines his invitation due to his health which allows him to attend only day affairs, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:37)
  - 1780 November 11 Archibald Steel Receipt from John Gibson, [merchant?] at Fort Pitt, 15,000 pounds Pennsylvania currency in Congress money for one pre-emption right for 1,000 acres of land, lying in the county of Youghiogheny, Pennsylvania, 1 page (6435-n) (Box-folder 11:38)
  - 1873 February 22 Alexander Hamilton Stephens (1812-1883) to Paul Hamilton Hayne (1830-1886), wishes he had seen him on his recent visit to Augusta as he had many matters to talk over with him, 4 pages on 1 l., with handwritten transcript (6435) (Box-folder 11:39)
  - 1881 October 22 Alexander Hamilton Stephens (1812-1883) to Paul Hamilton Hayne (1830-1886), thinks his poem to President Arthur excellent in tone and language; does not give much attention to spiritualism or animal magnetism, since he cannot understand it; plans to asks the editor of The Democrat to republish his poem on Garfield; and reports favorably on his recent health. 3 pages on 1 l., perhaps in a different hand than previous letter (6435) (Box-folder 11:39)
  - 1912 May 8 Henry L. Stimson (1867-1950) to the Reverend Paul R. Hickok, Washington, D.C., thanks him for his kind words about the memorial exercises for Major Butt, 1 typewritten page (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:40)
  - 1885 December 17 Frank R. Stockton (1834-1902) to Mrs. Dodge, [secretary to Amelie (Rives) Troubetzkoy, (1863-1945)], sends by express samples of apples from the Piedmont region, including yellow "Albemarle Pippins," red "Winesaps," and "Lady Apples.", 3 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:41)
  - 1844 June 22 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Robert B. Bagby, recommends that he settle his claim on John W. Brockenbrough (who denies responsibility entirely) through arbitration, suggests some names for the arbitrator and offers his services for either arbitration or a lawsuit, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:42)
  - 1852 January 29 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Lewis Jacob Cist (1818-1885), agrees to comply with his unnamed request, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:43)
  - 1868 August 12 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Henry R. Howland, confirms the dates of his own political service, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:44)
  - 1873 September 3 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to John Neafie, furnishes the dates of his political service, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:45)
  - 1869 May 20 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to M.D. Phillips, lists ex-Governors of Virginia still living and their place of residence, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:46)
  - 1852 February 19 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to John B. Pollock, agrees to comply with his request, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:47)
  - 1886 November 25 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Charles E. Rice, has finally received his note and enclosures and hastens to comply with his request, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:48)
  - 1886 March 13 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to the Reverend Dr. E.F. Strickland, lists many of the men that he knew from the political sphere of over fifty years ago and shares his memories of Thomas Jefferson staying with his father for a few days in 1818 and dining with his parents at Monticello in 1823, 3 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:49)
  - 1887 March 17 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Harry P. Waitnight, sends an envelope with the signature of President Millard Fillmore to satisfy his request for a letter of Fillmore, none of which seemed appropriate to give away, 1 page on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:50)
  - 1853 October 22 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Messrs. William M. Morrison & Company, writes concerning a book order, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:51)
  - 1854 August 17 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) to Messrs. William M. Morrison & Company, writes concerning a book order, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:51)
  - 1852 April 28 Alexander H.H. Stuart (1807-1891) signature on a Department of the Interior form for an invalid pension for Joseph Clark, an ensign in Captain Schuyler's Company of the New York Militia, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:52)
  - 1900 April 18 John Bannister Tabb (1845-1909) to John Lane (1854-1925), hopes Lane has something to publish for his friend Dr. Thomas R. Price, asks if there is a chance of him getting Tabb's Child Verse as well as the other books, as he may have something along the same line to offer him for England if this war [Second Boer War?] ever ends, 2 pages on 1 l., with a news clipping concerning Tabb, August 27, 1946 (6435) (Box-folder 11:53)
  - 1832 January 27 John Taliaferro (1768-1852) to T[ristam] Burges (1770-1853), member of Congress from Rhode Island, informs him in a very picturesque and fanciful manner that the weather has prevented him from coming to see him in person in Washington and asks him to explain the principles of the case of the claims commutation of Edmond Brooke to Chairman [Henry Augustus Philip?] Muhlenberg of the Committee in Congress, that reported on it unfavorably, and to Mr. Foote of the Senate, 3 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:54)
  - 1825 July 7 Littleton Waller Tazewell (1774-1860) to "Dear Sir," asks for the amount of the check prefixed to be credited to the account of John N. Tazewell, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:55)
  - 1829 January 9 Littleton Waller Tazewell (1774-1860) to "Dear Sir," apologizes for his delay in response to his request but promises to provide him with autographs as soon as he returns home from Congress, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:55)
  - 1862 February 1 Dr. James H. Thompson, Steamship Constitution, Surgeon 12th Regiment, Maine Volunteers, to Dr. Gilman Kimball, General Hospital Surgeon, "Camp Chase," Lowell, Massachusetts, reports on measles and pneumonia cases and medicinal needs, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:56)
  - 1870 March 22 John Reuben Thompson (1823-1873), The Evening Post, to "My dear Johnson" [Benjamin Johnson Barbour (1821-1894)], asks if he has received any of the materials listed that he has sent him, mentions "a row in the office of The Evening Post and Gaudette and [Augustus] Maverick (1830-?) have resigned. Gaudette goes to Philadelphia in April. This breaks up the establishment at 250 State Street." He also notes that Maverick plans to sail for Europe in May, perhaps visiting him at Barboursville, Virginia beforehand., 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-r) (Box-folder 11:57)
  - 1860 December 15 John Reuben Thompson (1823-1873) to Charles Edward Bennett, sends his autograph, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:58)
  - 1850 August 11 John Reuben Thompson (1823-1873) to Miss Anna C. Lynch [Botta] (1815-1891), sends her a package of the numbers of The Southern Literary Messenger for 1850 and welcomes any contribution that she could make to the magazine; page two contains a "Sonnet to Miss Anna C. Lynch" by Thompson, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:59)
  - 1855 December 5 John Reuben Thompson (1823-1873) to Joseph Ripley Chandler (1792-1880), asks if Chandler can lecture on Tuesday and Thursday evenings, the 18th and 20th, or even on the 13th, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:60)
  - 1945 April 6-7 Randall Thompson (1899-1984) to Boaz Pillar, sends his autograph and a quote from Thomas Jefferson, 1 page, electrostatic copy of original in Vault-Autograph File (6435-w) (Box-folder 11:61)
  - 1858 September 2 George Ticknor (1791-1871) to "Mrs. Rogers" [Emma Savage Rogers], inquires about the health of her father, James Savage (1784-1873) of Boston, and offers assistance if there is anything they can do for her, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:62)
  - 1920 May 5 George Macaulay Trevelyan (1876-1962) to "Dear Sir," asks him to describe his proposal and if he thinks he can do it, he will arrange a meeting, 1 page (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:63)
  - 1874 June 12 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928), English historian and politician, to James Beal, writes "I am glad to hear that the Electoral Reform Association is moving in favor of a more just and effective representation of the country" and that he will be too busy for public engagements during the recess., 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:64)
  - 1880 November 13 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear Brassey," asks if the family of a certain young man at the Royal Naval Barracks is able to buy his discharge from service, 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:65)
  - 1893 January 7 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear Mrs. Stewart Brown," regrets that he is unable to leave London and attend the meeting of the Women's Liberal Federation before Parliament meets, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:66)
  - 1881 February 24 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to Mr. Heath, writes that according to Lord Northbrook's chief secretary, the nominations have been made before he received Heath's first letter, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:67)
  - 1895 February 13 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to Cyril N. Ir[?], considers his desire to join the Royal Irish Constabulary, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:68)
  - 1889 February 20 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear [Leveson?-] Gower, expresses great pleasure at meeting him for breakfast on [March] 2nd, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:69)
  - 1910 June 22 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to R [?] Lucas, answers questions about the Owl [Club?] dinners and members, and says he has a volume of the Owls since the beginning of 1866, when he joined them., 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:70)
  - 1892 January 16 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear Mrs. Macgregor," writes that the press of work prevents him from accepting her invitation, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:71)
  - 1890 November 8 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear Reid," is pleased to take the chair on December 2nd for every reason, includes a note on the back in another hand, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:72)
  - 1891 February 10 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to W[illiam] H[enry] Rideing (1853-1919), appreciates his offer of sending copies of The North American Review, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:73)
  - 1908 February 26 Sir George Otto Trevelyan (1838-1928) to "Dear [Scott?], writes that he is glad what he wrote met the requirements and discusses several points of Trevelyan genealogy, 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-av) (Box-folder 11:74)
  - 1869 April 2 Nicholas Philip Trist (1800-1874) to Henry C. Carey (1793-1879), replies that he is unable to attend Vespers because of continuing illness, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-s) (Box-folder 11:75)
  - 1832 November 13 Frances Trollope to Mary Russell Mitford, thanks her for both her book and her letter, and she has ordered the other four volumes of Our Village sketches about which she says, "The work is perfectly unique. I know nothing like it in any language, and it is among the few to which one can turn again and again and again with even new pleasure. The 'Farewell' is one of the sweetest bits of writing that I know." Mrs. Bentley reports that Covent Garden is beautiful and that the Kembles are doing wonders, with Charles being rich at last. Macready is out of fashion and should have played in her play "Rienzi." Trollope especially enjoyed the Bramshill scene, "I would give a joint of my little finger to visit Bramshill again.", 4 pages, on 1 l. (6435-a) (Box-folder 11:76)
  - [1893?] July 6 Prince Pierre Troubetzkoy (1864-1936) to Mr. Knowles, writes concerning the painting of [Prime Minister William] Gladstone's portrait, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435-a) (Box-folder 11:77)
  - 1945 December 4 Lt. General L[ucian] K[ing] Truscott, Jr. (1895-1965) to Howes Norris, Jr., agrees to furnish an autograph for his collection, 1 typewritten page (6435-at) (Box-folder 11:78)
  - 1871 February 24 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871), essayist and critic, to Anne Charlotte (Lynch) Botta (1815-1891), hopes this autograph (not present) of Mr. Kennedy just received from Baltimore will serve her purpose, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:79)
  - n.y. March 9 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Anne Charlotte (Lynch) Botta (1815-1891), sends her a volume delayed in printing since the first impression was exhausted, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:79)
  - n.y. May 3 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Anne Charlotte (Lynch) Botta (1815-1891), agrees to meet her early next week and to look over the sheets of her book concerning American literature, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:79)
  - n.y. November [23] Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Anne Charlotte (Lynch) Botta (1815-1891), promises to try to meet her for breakfast tomorrow, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:79)
  - 1863 December 24 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to [Francis James?] Child (1825-1896), writes that his copy of the Gazette has arrived, does not think he has anything that would answer for the L.G., unless any of his addenda to his books, literary & reviews, would answer, and is not impressed with the first number of the "Round Table.", 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:80)
  - 1860 November 24 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to James Thomas Fields (1817-1881), asks if it would be agreeable and convenient to publish a volume in the spring, "this quite in your line & consists of papers which have proved successful in periodicals & were originally written with a view to collection." 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:81)
  - 1861 October 29 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to James Thomas Fields (1817-1881), sends a poem for The Atlantic and asks for a proof, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:81)
  - 1860 August 24 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Josiah L. Hale, asks his help in locating information about his grandfather's French claims or any agent employed by the Washington Insurance Company, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:82)
  - 1864 April 22 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Josiah Gilbert Holland (1819-1881), complies with his request, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:83)
  - n.y. October 9 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Oscar T. Keeler, regrets he has no autographs of [Lentze?], 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:84)
  - 1839 February 27 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Messrs. Lea & Blanchard, asks them to answer by return mail the earliest day they will be able to put his book to press, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:85)
  - 1859 March 1 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Benson John Lossing (1813-1891), asks questions concerning the Peale portrait of Washington at Arlington House and would appreciate any corrections to his article "Original Portraits of Washington." Putnam's Monthly 6 (October 1855): 345-347., 3 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:86)
  - 1859 September 21 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Benson John Lossing (1813-1891), asks him to direct Joseph Harper to send the autograph copy of the Field Book to the Studio Building, expresses his surprise and deep disappointment at Mr. Putnam's decision not to publish his little books on Washington's character and portraits, and asks Lossing to encourage Putnam to reconsider, 4 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:86)
  - n.d. Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Benson John Lossing (1813-1891), informs him that [Lentze?] has agreed to meet with him at Lossing's house and asks him to have any of his sketches on the Battle of Monmouth or the Boston Tea Party on hand, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:86)
  - 1870 April 6 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to George E. Patten, lists his most popular poem descriptions of the seasons and where they were published including A Sheaf of Verse Bound for the Fair and Indian Summer, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:87)
  - 1851 December 9 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Anna Cora (Ogden) Mowatt Ritchie (1819-1870), suspects Virginia Governor [John Buchanan Floyd's?] ignorance of art based on his speech on the inauguration of Houdon's statue, and his plan to have Randolph Rogers complete the statues of Marshall, Nelson, Lewis and the allegorical figures, on the equestrian statue of George Washington and Monument, Capitol Grounds, begun by Thomas Crawford, designer of the complex and sculptor of the figures of Washington, Jefferson, Henry and Mason, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:88)
  - n.y. March 30 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Edmund Clarence Stedman (1833-1908), expresses his pleasure that he enjoyed his review of his Stedman's book about Kinney, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:89)
  - n.y. December 24 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to S. Stevens, regrets that he was out when he called but will make a list of the right people to apply to, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:90)
  - 1866 August 21 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Edwin Percy Whipple (1819-1886), asks if he knows how a lecturer proceeds to find engagements, so he can assist a friend, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:91)
  - 1853 May 2 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to Nathaniel Parker Willis (1806-1867), asks him to reconsider his policy change about not having literature notices in the Home Journal except for editorial ones, 4 pages on 1 l., with typed transcript (6435) (Box-folder 11:92)
  - 1842 November 2 Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to "My dear Sir," asks for a contribution to the Boston Miscellany, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:93)
  - n.d. Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) to "My dear Sir," illegible draft, 1 page (6435) (Box-folder 11:93)
  - n.d. Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) Poem "A Reminiscence" (6435) (Box-folder 11:94)
  - 1859, n.d. Henry Theodore Tuckerman (1813-1871) Untitled Poems (Box-folder 11:95)
  - 1865 February 24 Martin Farquhar Tupper (1810-1889) to Mr. Bennock, agrees to come and dine with the feasting Judges and Sheriffs, calls himself a temperance man in all things, and promises to send some reprints of colonial editors, 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-a) (Box-folder 11:96)
  - 1856 November 11 Martin Farquhar Tupper (1810-1889) to Henry Cole, declines to join the Association and to accept the office of Treasurer, 1 page (6435-a) (Box-folder 11:97)
  - n.y. April 23 Martin Farquhar Tupper (1810-1889) to Miss Mayne, thanks her for her note and specimen paper, "the name whereof and general appearance are all that can be wished for." Tupper also warns her against disseminating infidel and immoral periodicals in order to refute them, "when The Reasoner has a circulation of only 160 - you advertize him well, I fear, & why reveal to more men the sneering Gibbonism of The Lancashire Beacon?", 4 pages on 1 l. (6435-a) (Box-folder 11:98)
  - 1892 March 27 Lyon G. Tyler (1853-1935) to Charles Elmer Rice, writes that he would be happy to receive information about Nathaniel Tyler, a Lt. Colonel, in the Revolution, 2 pages on 1 l. (6435) (Box-folder 11:99)
  - 1964 November 14 Margaret Hench Underwood (1929-?) to her parents, Atcheson and Virginia Hench, describes the Profiles in Courage television program about Oscar Wilder Underwood, 1 typewritten page, with news clipping about the show (6435-ap) (Box-folder 11:100)
  - 1921 January 20 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Emil P. Albrecht, writes that he does not favor the proposed daylight savings bill, 1 typewritten page (6435-n) (Box-folder 11:101)
  - 1920 January 12 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Frederick L. Allen, although originally standing for unconditional ratification of the treaty of peace, he now believes "we should make a compromise and join in the peace of the world at an early date,", 1 typewritten page (6435-ak) (Box-folder 11:102)
  - 1910 February 14 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Court of Customs Appeals, Washington, D.C., recommends Thomas H. Clark of Alabama for Clerk of their court, 1 typewritten page (6435-ak) (Box-folder 11:103)
  - 1911 October 29 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Charles A. Edwards, informs him that he does not intend on presenting himself as a Presidential candidate for next year, 1 typewritten page (6435-l) (Box-folder 11:104)
  - 1911 November 10 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Charles A. Edwards, says that an effort to organize a publicity bureau on his behalf in Washington would be an embarrassment, 1 typewritten page (6435-l) (Box-folder 11:104)
  - 1911 December 18 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Charles A. Edwards, agrees to assist him in finding employment, 1 typewritten page (6435-l) (Box-folder 11:104)
  - 1909 February 9 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to Jules Guthridge, sends his autograph, 1 typewritten page (6435-ak) (Box-folder 11:105)
  - 1925 November 27 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to S. Hollister Jackson, American Granite Association, regrets he cannot accept his kind invitation, 1 typewritten page (6435-ak) (Box-folder 11:106)
  - 1910 March 8 Oscar W. Underwood (1862-1929) to E.D. Lee, promises to support the bill to allow the telepost company to erect its plant in the District of Columbia, 1 typewritten page (6435-ak) (Box-folder 11:107)